vyatta.org 2015-06-07

# Company

**Privacy Statement**   
Privacy is important to Brocade Communications Systems, Inc. ("Brocade" or "we"). This privacy policy explains Brocade's web site and services (collectively, the "Service"). Effective Date: June 17, 2004. 

If you feel that Brocade is not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact the Webmaster at [privacy@brocade.com](mailto:privacy@brocade.com). 

**Information Collection and Use**  
We collect the following personally identifiable information about our users: name, e-mail address, telephone number, business address, shipping address, social security number, preferred means of communication, credit card information and other information voluntarily provided. This personally identifiable information is typically provided when users register for online services, purchase products online, or participate in contests, surveys or sweepstakes. We also collect information about users regarding web pages accessed, traffic patterns and site usage. 

We, our service providers and our vendors may use any information collected by users: to operate the Service; to effect users' transactions; to provide better services, products and opportunities to users; to notify users about services, products and opportunities that may be of interest to such users; to create and share reports about users' transactions; and for other marketing purposes. We may also trade, sell, rent or otherwise share your personally identifiable information with other third parties, including our business partners.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information stored on your hard drive containing information about you. These pieces of information allow the Service to remember important information that will make your use of the Service more useful. Brocade uses cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, we use cookies to allow your automated login and to track your preferences and usage. You can choose to reject or turn off the cookies through your browser settings. If you reject or turn off the cookies, you may still use the Service. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of the Service. For example, you will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes, contests or monthly drawings that we may offer.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Service, track users' movements, and gather demographic information.

**Security**  
We use security measures, such as firewalls and Security Socket Layers ("SSL"), to safeguard the confidentiality of our users' personally identifiable information. Information we collect about our users is stored on secured servers. However, "perfect security" does not exist. If you have any questions about the security of the Service, please send an e-mail to [privacy@brocade.com](mailto:privacy@brocade.com).

**Minors**  
Minors (individuals below the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Service and no portion of the Service is directed towards minors. We do not knowingly solicit any information about minors or market to minors.

**Disclosure Required by Law**  
We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use the Service for illegal activities. Therefore, we respond to subpoenas, warrants or other court orders regarding information concerning any users. We will, at our discretion, disclose information if we believe that we are required to do so by law, that such disclosure is necessary to protect us from legal liability or that we should do so to protect the integrity of the Service.

**Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire Brocade's services, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the data you provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by sending an e-mail to [privacy@brocade.com](mailto:privacy@brocade.com).

**Your Consent; Notification of Changes**  
By using the Service, you consent to Brocade's collection and use of the information described in this privacy policy. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes via our homepage so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of an e-mail. Please check this policy from time to time to make sure that you are aware of our latest privacy policy.
